根据BDRip TLF版本重新调整字幕
by:forgetted@tlf
本字幕仅供学习交流
切勿用于交流用途
片名：《闪灵》
面试
嗨 我跟乌尔曼先生约好了的
Hi. I've got an appointment with Mr. Ullman.
我叫杰克.托兰斯
My name is Jack Torrance.
在左边第一个门进去就是他办公室
His office is the first door on the left.
谢谢
Thank you.
乌尔曼先生?
Mr. Ullman?
我是杰克.托兰斯
I'm Jack Torrance.
快进来 杰克
Come on in, Jack.
-很高兴见到你      -我也是
-Very nice to meet you.     -Nice to meet you.
这是我的秘书 苏茜
This is my secretary, Susie.
-苏茜 你好么?
-这地方不难找吧?
-Susie, how do you do?
-Any trouble finding us?
很好找 我在路上花了三个半小时
No problem at all. I made the trip in 3 1/2 hours.
不过旅途非常愉快
That's very good time.
坐会吧 杰克
Sit down a minute, Jack.
随便点
Just make yourself at home.
要来点咖啡么?
Like some coffee?
如果有的话就来点 谢谢
If you're having some, I wouldn't mind. Thanks.
苏茜     好的
Susie.     Sure.
去叫比尔.沃森过来
And ask Bill Watson to join us.
好的 这就去
Yes, I will.
妈妈
Mom?
干吗
Yeah?
你真的想整个冬天都呆在那间酒店里么?
Do you really want to go and live in that hotel for the winter?
当然啦
Sure I do.
会很好玩的
It'll be lots of fun.
是的 我想也是
Yeah. I guess so.
不过 那里肯定没什么人跟我一起玩了
Anyway, there's hardly anybody to play with around here.
我知道 反正你也不怎么去交新朋友
I know. It always takes a little time to make new friends.
是的 我觉得也是
Yeah, I guess so.
托尼怎么样了
What about Tony?
我打赌他肯定很向往去酒店住
He's looking forward to the hotel, I bet.
不 我不想呢 托兰斯夫人
No, I ain't, Mrs. Torrance.
好了 别这样 托尼 别傻了
Now, come on, Tony. Don't be silly.
我不想去
I don't want to go there.
你怎么会不想去呢?
How come you don't want to go?
我就是不想去
I just don't.
在丹佛 他们有告诉过你
Did they give you any idea in Denver...
具体的工作职责么?
...about what the job entails?
只是总体上讲了一下
Only in a very general way.
这儿的冬天会非常的可怕
The winters can be fantastically cruel.
基本上来说 你的工作就是要防止可能发生的
The basic idea is to cope with the very costly damage...
重大损失和破坏
...and depreciation which can occur.
其中包括要开动汽锅
This consists mainly of running the boiler...
每天轮流给酒店的不同部分送热
...heating different parts of the hotel on a daily rotating basis...
并在出现损坏的时候进行维修工作
...repairing damage as it occurs...
并且做好维护工作 别让大自然把这儿毁了
...and doing repairs so the elements can't get a foothold.
我觉得应该没问题
That sounds fine to me.
就身体方面来说 这工作并不难
Physically, it's not a very demanding job.
唯一让人觉得难受的就是这儿的冬天
The only thing that can get a bit trying here during the winter...
会让你觉得孤独难耐
...is a tremendous sense of isolation.
这正是我想要的
That just happens to be exactly what I'm looking for.
我正在构思一本新书
I'm outlining a new writing project.
五个月的平静正是我想要的
Five months of peace is just what I want.
那就太好了 杰克
That's very good, Jack.
因为 对有些人来说
Because, for some people...
孤独
solitude
和与世隔绝
and isolation
本身可能就是个大问题
...can, of itself, become a problem.
对我来说不是的
Not for me.
那你的妻子和儿子呢?
他们能受得了么?
How about your wife and son?
Do you think they'll take to it?
他们也会很喜欢的
They'll love it.
太好了
Great.
在比尔带你去熟悉环境之前
Before I turn you over to Bill...
我想还有件事情我们得谈谈
there's one other thing I think we should talk about.
并不是想搞得很戏剧性
Not to sound melodramatic...
但是 知道这件事情会让某些人
...but it's been known to give a few people...
对这份工作有所迟疑的
...second thoughts about the job.
你勾起了我的好奇心
I'm intrigued.
我想他们在丹佛并没有跟你说过
I don't suppose they said anything in Denver...
在一九七零年这儿发生过桩悲剧
...about the tragedy we had up here during the winter of 1970.
他们确实没有提起过
I don't believe they did.
以前干我这个职位的前辈
My predecessor in this job...
雇了一个叫查尔斯.格兰蒂的人做冬季看守
...hired a man named Charles Grady as the winter caretaker.
他和他的妻子以及两个女儿 一个八岁 一个十岁
He came up with his wife and 2 little girls of about 8 and 10.
他的履历非常好 而且倍受推崇
He had a good employment record, good references.
就我所知 他好像
And from what I've been told, he seemed...
看起来是个绝对正常的人
...like a completely normal individual.
但是 就在那年冬天某个时候
But at some point during the winter...
他好像是彻底精神崩溃了
he must have suffered some kind of a complete mental breakdown.
就疯了
He ran amuck...
拿斧头砍死了自己的家人
...and killed his family with an ax.
然后把他们整洁得放在西翼的一间房里
Stacked them neatly in a room in the west wing
之后 就吞枪自杀了
and then... he put both barrels of his shotgun in his mouth.
警方认为
The police thought...
他就是患上了以前所说的幽居病
...that it was what the old-timers used to call cabin fever.
如果人们长时间被关在某一地方
A kind of claustrophobic reaction which can occur...
就会产生这种幽居恐惧症
when people are shut in together over long periods of time.
这真是
That is...
够戏剧性的了
...quite a story.
是的 确实
Yeah, it is.
我还是很难相信这儿发生过这种事
It's still hard for me to believe it actually happened here.
不过确实发生过
But it did.
我想你能理解我告诉你这件事的原因
I think you can appreciate why I wanted to tell you about it.
当然
I certainly can.
而且我也明白为什么你在丹佛的同事
I also understand why your people in Denver...
会留给你来告诉我这件事
...left it for you to tell me.
很显然 有些人会因为这地方
Obviously, some people can be put off...
发生过那种事而退缩的
from staying in a place where something like that happened.
您大可放心 这种事不会发生在我身上的
You can rest assured that's not going to happen with me.
至于我妻子的话
And as far as my wife is concerned...
我肯定她听到这事会无比兴奋的
...I'm sure she'll be absolutely fascinated when I tell her.
她对鬼故事
She's a confirmed ghost story...
和恐怖电影非常着迷
...and horror film addict.
托尼 你觉得爸爸会得到这份工作么?
Tony, do you think Dad'll get the job?
他已经得到了
He already did.
过几分钟 他就会打电话来告诉温蒂了
He 's going to phone Wendy up in a few minutes to tell her.
嗨 宝贝    嗨 亲爱的怎么样了?
Hi, babe.  Hi, hon. How's it going?
太好了 我已经在酒店了还有很多事得做
Great. I'm at the hotel and I still have a lot to go through.
我想可能九点十点都回不来的了
I don't think I can get home before 9:00 or 10:00.
看来你好像是得到这份工作了
Sounds like you got the job.
是的 这儿很美
Right. It's a beautiful place.
你和丹尼肯定会喜欢这儿的
You and Danny are going to love it.
托尼 你为什么不想去酒店?
Tony, why don't you want to go to the hotel?
我不知道
I don't know.
你肯定知道 现在 快点告诉我吧
You do too know. Now come on, tell me.
我不想说
I don't want to.
求你了
Please.
不
No.
来吧 托尼 告诉我吧
Now, Tony, tell me.
我们肯定已经上到很高的地方了
空气都完全不同的呢
We must really be high up.
The air feels so different.
爸爸
Dad?
我饿了
I'm hungry.
你应该把早餐吃了的
You should've eaten your breakfast.
我们一到酒店就给你弄点东西吃 好么?
We'll get you something as soon as we get to the hotel.
好的 妈妈
Okay, Mom.
这不就是当纳聚会受风雪围困的地方么?
Wasn't it around here that the Donner party got snowbound?
我想应该还要再往西点 在深山里
I think that was farther west, in the Sierras.
什么是当纳聚会呀?
What was the Donner party?
是指还在使用马车的年代的一群拓荒者
They were a party of settlers in covered wagon times.
在某个冬天被风雪围困在了山里
They got snowbound one winter in the mountains.
他们不得不嗜食同类以生存下去
They had to resort to cannibalism in order to stay alive.
你是说人吃人?
You mean they ate each other up?
为了生存 他们不得不这么做
They had to in order to survive.
杰克
Jack.
别担心 妈妈
Don't worry, Mom.
我知道人吃人的事 电视里都有播
I know all about cannibalism. I saw it on TV.
看吧 没事的
See, it's okay.
他都在电视上看过了
He saw it all on the television.
飞机几点起飞     八点半
What time does the plane leave?   8:30.
那我们就有足够的时间来收拾东西
That gives us plenty of time to go over everything.
再见 乌尔曼先生    再见
Goodbye, Mr. Ullman.     Bye.
早上好 我希望你们没有等得太久
Good morning. I hope you haven't been waiting too long.
没关系 我们有时间来吃点东西
No problem. We had time to grab a bite to eat.
很好 很高兴你在厨房关闭之前到达了
Good. Glad you made it before they shut down the kitchen.
你的家人四处参观去了?
Is your family having a look around?
还没呢 我儿子发现了游戏室
No, my son's discovered the games room.
你们的行李拿进来了么?      都在那儿了
Has your luggage been brought in?   Right there.
由于我们得在今天搞定一切
In view of all we have to cover today...
我想我们还是快去看看你们的房间 开始工作
l suggest we have a quick look at your apartment and get started.
把托兰斯的行李送到他们的房间去
Have the Torrances' things brought to their apartment.
我得先把我的家人都找回来
I'd better collect my family first.
这是科罗拉多休闲室
This is our Colorado Lounge.
真漂亮
It's beautiful.
天哪
My God!
这地方真棒 对吧 亲爱的
This place is fantastic, isn't it, hon?
当然
It sure is.
这是酒店的员工翼
This is the staff wing of the hotel.
冬季其它房间都不会供热
None of the other bedrooms are heated during the winter.
再见 乌尔曼先生     再见 姑娘们
Goodbye, Mr. Ullman.    Goodbye, girls.
这儿就是你们的住处
And here are your quarters.
客厅 卧室 洗手间
Living room, bedroom, bathroom.
这间小卧室是你儿子的
And a small bedroom for your son.
给孩子住恰倒好处
Perfect for a child.
远望酒店是什么时候修建的?
When was the Overlook built?
一九零七年始建
Construction started in 1907.
一九零九年才完工
It was finished in 1909.
这地方本来是印第安坟场
The site's supposed to be on an Indian burial ground.
所以在修建期间
They actually had to repel...
还击退了几次印第安人的袭击
...a few Indian attacks as they were building it.
那是雪地车
That's our Snowcat.
-你们俩都会开车吧  -是的
-Can you both drive a car?  -Yes.
很好 基本上雪地车的操作跟汽车差不多
That's fine. Basically the Snowcat operates very much like a car.
用不了多久你们就能熟练操作的了
It won't take you long to get the hang of it.
这就是厨房么 哈?
This is the kitchen, huh?
是的
This is it.
你喜欢么 丹尼? 对你来说够大了么?
How do you like it, Danny? Is it big enough for you?
是我见过最大的厨房了
It's the biggest place I ever seen.
这地方就跟个迷宫似的
This whole place is such an enormous maze.
估计我每次进来都得撒面包屑做标记
I'll have to leave a trail of breadcrumbs every time I come in.
别让它把你吓坏了
Don't let it get you down.
这儿再大也不过就是个厨房而已
It's big, but it ain't nothing but a kitchen.
有很多东西你根本就不需要碰
A lot of this stuff you'll never have to touch.
就算碰了 我也不知道该怎么弄
I wouldn't know what to do with it if I did.
有一件事情是肯定的 就是你不用为吃的担心
One thing for sure, you don't have to worry about food.
你们能在这儿吃上一年
而且还每天都能吃到不同的菜色
You folks could eat here for a year
and never have the same menu twice.
这是小型冷藏间
Right here is our walk-in freezer.
所有的肉都冷藏在这里面
This is where we keep all of our meat.
十五条烟熏肋骨
You got 15 rib roasts...
三十袋十镑一袋的碎牛肉
...30 ten-pound bags of hamburger.
十二只火鸡 大约四十只小鸡
We got 12 turkeys, about 40 chickens...
五十个腰肉牛排 两打烟熏猪肉
...50 sirloin steaks, two dozen of pork roast...
二十条羔羊腿 你喜欢羔羊肉么 医生?
-不.
...and 20 legs of lamb. Do you like lamb, Doc?
-No.
不喜欢? 那你最喜欢吃什么呢?
You don't? What's your favorite food, then?
炸薯条加番茄酱
French fries and ketchup.
我想我们也能弄出那玩意来吃的 医生
I think we can manage that too, Doc.
现在过这边来 小心脚下
Come along, now. Watch your step.
哈罗朗先生 你怎么知道我们叫他医生?
How'd you know we call him Doc?
-抱歉
-医生 你叫了丹尼两次医生
-Beg your pardon?
Doc. You called Danny "Doc" twice.
我有么？
I did?
我们有时叫他医生 就像兔巴哥卡通里一样
We call him Doc sometimes, like in the Bugs Bunny cartoons.
不过 你是怎么知道的呢
But how did you know?
我想我可能是听到你这么叫他了
I guess I probably heard you call him that.
有可能 不过 老实说 我确实不记得
It's possible. But I honestly don't remember...
在见到你之后 有那样叫过他
...calling him that since we've been with you.
不管怎样 他看起来就像是个医生 不是么?
Anyway, he looks like a Doc, doesn't he?
你好么 医生?
What's up, Doc?
这是间库房
Now, this is the storeroom.
所有的干货和罐装食物
In here is where we keep...
都储藏在这儿
...all the dried goods and the canned goods.
有水果罐头 蔬菜罐头
We got canned fruits and vegetables...
鱼罐头 肉罐头 冷热水冲调的谷物
...canned fish and meats, hot and cold cereals.
烤面包片 玉米片 泡芙
Post Toasties, Corn Flakes, Sugar Puffs...
萨琪玛 燕麦片 小麦 还有麦乳
Rice Krispies, oatmeal, Wheatena and Cream of Wheat.
还有十二壶蜜糖
You got a dozen jugs of black molasses.
六十盒干奶
We got 60 boxes of dried milk...
来点冰淇淋怎么样 医生?
How'd you like some ice cream, Doc?
各种小吃 甜点
Sociables, finger rolls...
要什么有什么
...and 7 kinds of what have you.
这边还有桃干杏干
Now, we've got dried peaches, dried apricots...
葡萄干还有洋李干
...dried raisins and dried prunes.
你知道的 要想过得轻松开心点就得把一切都弄清楚
You know, you got to keep regular if you want to be happy.
怎么样了?     很好
How're you getting on?     Fine.
能把托兰斯夫人借我们用用不?
我们要去地下室看看
Can we borrow Mrs. Torrance?
We're on our way to the basement.
我保证不会很久的
I promise we won't keep her very long.
没问题 乌尔曼先生 我正要去拿冰淇淋呢
No problem, Mr. Ullman. I was just getting to the ice cream.
要来点冰淇淋么 医生?     好的
You like ice cream, Doc?     Yes.
我就知道你想吃
I thought you did.
在你们回来之前 不介意我带丹尼去吃点冰淇淋吧?
You folks mind if I give Danny some ice cream while we wait?
当然不     我们不介意
Not at all.     We don't mind.
很好     你觉得怎么样 医生?
Good.     Sound good to you, Doc?
好的 要乖点哟
Okay, you behave yourself.
你喜欢吃哪种冰淇淋呢
What kind of ice cream do you like?
巧克力的
Chocolate.
巧克力的 没问题 来吧 孩子
Chocolate it shall be. Come on, son.
今天真是太充实了
It's amazing, all this activity today.
住客和一些员工昨天就走了 不过
The guests and some staff left yesterday, but the...
最后一天总是让人很忙乱
...last day's always hectic.
人人都想尽早离开
Everybody wants to be on their way as early as possible.
到今天下午五点 这儿就跟没人来过一样
By 5:00 tonight, you'll never know anybody was ever here.
就跟间鬼店一样 哈?
Just like a ghost ship, huh?
你知道我怎么知道你叫医生的么?
Do you know how I knew your name was Doc?
你知道我在说什么 对吧?
You know what I'm talking about, don't you?
我记得自己还是个孩子的时候
I can remember when I was a little boy...
我和我奶奶可以
my grandmother and I could hold conversations
不张嘴就聊天
entirely without ever opening our mouths.
她把这叫做闪灵
She called it "shining."
很长一段时间 我都觉得只有我们俩会
And for a long time I thought it was just the two of us...
才拥有这种闪灵交流
...that had "the shine" to us.
正如你可能认为只有你一个人一样
Just like you probably thought you was the only one.
不过 还有的人也跟我们一样
But there are other folks...
尽管他们大多不知道 或者是不相信
though mostly they don't know it, or don't believe it.
你有这种能力多长时间了?
How long have you been able to do it?
你为什么不想说这个?
Why don't you want to talk about it?
我不能说的
I'm not supposed to.
谁说你不能说
Who says you ain't supposed to?
托尼
Tony.
谁是托尼?
Who's Tony?
托尼是住在我嘴里的小男孩
Tony's the little boy that lives in my mouth.
托尼就是那个
Is Tony the one that...
告诉你某些事情的人?     是的
...tells you things?     Yes.
他怎么告诉你这些事情的？
How does he tell you the thing?
就像是我睡觉的时候 他就给我看
It's like I go to sleep, and he shows me things.
但是等我醒过来 并不记得所有的事情
But when I wake up, I can't remember everything.
你爸爸妈妈知道托尼的事么?
Does your mom and dad know about Tony?
他们知道他会告诉你些事情么?
Do they know he tells you things?
托尼叫我绝不能告诉他们
Tony told me never to tell them.
托尼有没有跟你提过这地方的事?
Has Tony ever told you anything about this place?
关于远望酒店么?
About the Overlook Hotel?
我不知道
I don't know.
现在 好好想想 医生.  想想看.
Now think real hard, Doc. Think.
这儿有些坏东西么?
Is there something bad here?
你知道么 医生 如果有事发生的话
You know, Doc, when something happens...
都会遗留下可寻的线索
it can leave a trace of itself behind.
你看 就像
Say, like...
某人是不是烤糊了面包片
...if someone burns toast.
或许其他事情还会留下其他一些线索
Maybe things that happen leave other kind of traces behind.
而那些线索并不是任何人都能发现的
Not things that anyone can notice.
但却是拥有闪灵能力的人能看得见的
But things that people who shine can see.
就像他们能看到还未发生的事情
Just like they can see things that haven't happened yet...
有时又能看到很久之前发生过的事情
sometimes they can see things that happened a long time ago.
我想这些年 在这间酒店
I think a lot of things happened right here...
发生了很多事情
in this particular hotel over the years.
而且发生的并不都是好事
And not all of them was good.
二三七号房怎么回事呢?
What about room 237?
二三七号房?
Room 237?
你害怕二三七号房 是么?
You're scared of room 237, ain't you?
不 我不怕
No, I ain't.
哈罗朗先生 二三七号房里有什么吗?
Mr. Hallorann, what is in room 237?
没什么
Nothing.
二三七号房里什么都没有
There ain't nothing in room 237.
不过 你要没事可千万别去那儿
But you ain't got no business going in there anyway.
离那房间远点
So stay out.
明白么? 离那儿远点
You understand? Stay out!
早上好 亲爱的
Good morning, hon.
早饭准备好了
Your breakfast is ready.
现在几点了?
What time is it?
大概十一点半了
It's about 11:30.
十一点半了 天哪
11:30. Jesus.
我想昨天晚上是熬得太晚了
I guess we've been staying up too late.
我知道
I know it.
我都照你喜欢的口味做的 单面的煎蛋
I made them just the way you like them, sunny-side up.
很好
Nice.
外面真是够漂亮的
It's really pretty outside.
吃完早餐跟我一起去散散步怎么样?
How about taking me for a walk after you finish your breakfast?
我想我应该先写点东西
I suppose I ought to try to do some writing first.
有灵感了么?
Any ideas yet?
灵感倒是不少
Lots of ideas.
就是没一个好的
No good ones.
一切都会好的
Something will come.
只是得养成每天都进行写作的习惯
It's just a matter of settling into the habit of writing every day.
就是这样
That's all it is.
好的     你输定了
All right.     And you're going to lose.
我会抓住你的 你最好跑快点
And I'm going to get you. You'd better run fast!
小心
Look out!
我来啦
I'm coming in close.
输了的要去做清洁哟
Loser has to keep America clean.
做清洁哟
Keep America clean.
丹尼 你赢了
Danny, you win.
我们还是用走的吧
Let's take the rest of this walking.
把手给我
Give me your hand.
漂亮吧?     是的
Isn't it beautiful?   Yes.
死路
Dead end.
我们走出来了
We made it.
漂亮吧?
Isn't it beautiful?
确实很漂亮
It's so pretty.
我可没想到有这么大呢 你呢?   没呢
I didn't think it was going to be this big. Did you?   No.
嗨 亲爱的
Hi, hon.
怎么样了?
How's it going?
很好
Fine.
今天写了很多东西吧    是的
Get a lot written today?      Yes.
很好 天气预报说今天会下雪呢
Good. The weather forecast said it's going to snow tonight.
你想让我怎么对付暴风雪呢?
What do you want me to do about it?
别这样 亲爱的
Come on, hon.
别板着脸不高兴的样子
Don't be so grouchy.
我没有
I'm not...
不高兴
...being grouchy.
我只是想快把书写完
I just want to finish my work.
好的 我明白
Okay. I understand.
我等会再拿些三明治过来
I'll come back later with a couple of sandwiches.
说不定 到时你还能让我看看你写的东西
Maybe you'll let me read something then.
温蒂
Wendy...
我跟你解释一下吧
...let me explain something to you.
你只要进来打岔 就会让我分心
When you come in and interrupt, you're breaking my concentration.
你在转移我的注意力
You're distracting me...
我又得花不少时间才能弄清楚刚才到哪儿了
...and it will then take me time to get back to where I was.
明白么?     是的
Understand?     Yes.
很好
Fine.
我们现在定几条规矩吧
We're going to make a new rule:
只要我在这儿
Whenever I'm in here...
你又听到打字的声音
...and you hear me typing...
或者不管你他妈听到我在这儿干吗
...or whatever the fuck you hear me doing in here...
反正 我在这儿 就说明我在工作
...when I'm in here, that means I am working.
也就是说 你不能进来
That means don't come in.
那么 你想你能做到么?     是的
Now, do you think you can handle that?
好吧
Fine.
那你他妈怎么还不给我滚出去?
Why don't you start right now and get the fuck out of here?
没打中
Missed!
你手里没雪球咯
Don't have!
现在可轮到我动手了
No fair anymore.
早就知道了
I knew it.
KDK 12呼叫KDK 1
This is KDK 12 calling KDK 1 .
KDK 12 to KDK 1.
我是KDK 1 收到你的呼叫 完毕
This is KDK 1. We're receiving you. Over.
嗨 我是温蒂.托兰斯 现在远望酒店
Hi, this is Wendy Torrance at the Overlook Hotel.
嗨 你们在上边过得怎么样呀? 完毕
Hi, how are you folks getting on up there? Over.
过得还不错
We're just fine.
不过电话老是出问题
But our telephones aren't doing too well.
会不会是电话线桩倒了? 完毕
Are the lines down, by any chance? Over.
是的 有好几个都给暴风雪打断了 完毕
Yes, quite a few of them are down due to the storm. Over.
有没有可能很快就修好呢? 完毕
Any chance of them being repaired soon? Over.
恩 估计不行
Well, I wouldn't like to say.
一般冬天他们都不会去那儿 得到春天来了 完毕
Most winters they stay that way until spring. Over.
帅哥 这场暴风雪确实很可怕 对吧? 完毕
Boy, this storm is really something, isn't it? Over.
是的 是我们这些年遇到过的最可怕的
Yes. It's one of the worst we've had for years.
还有什么能为您做的么 托兰斯夫人?
Is there anything else we can do for you, Mrs. Torrance?
我想没有了 完毕
I suppose not. Over.
如果你们在上边遇到什么问题 就马上来电
If you folks have any problems up there, just give us a call.
还有 托兰斯夫人?
And, Mrs. Torrance?
如果你们能一直把无线电开着就好了
It might be a good idea if you leave your radio on all the time.
好的 我们会照做的
Okay. We'll do that.
能跟您聊会真是太好了
It was real nice talking to you.
再见 完毕 挂机
Bye. Over and out.
哈罗 丹尼
Hello, Danny.
过来跟我们一起玩吧
Come and play with us.
过来跟我们一起玩吧 丹尼
Come and play with us, Danny.
永远
Forever...
...and ever...
永远
...and ever.
托尼
Tony...
我害怕
...I'm scared.
还记得哈罗朗先生说得话么?
Remember what Mr. Hallorann said.
这就跟书里的图片一样丹尼
It's just like pictures in a book, Danny.
都不是真的
It isn't real.
我能上我房间去把消防车拿过来么?
Can I go up to my room and get my fire engine?
先过来一下
Come here for a minute first.
你怎么样呀 医生?
How's it going, Doc?
过得还开心么?
Having a good time?
开心 爸爸
Yes, Dad.
很好
Good.
我就想让你过得开心
I want you to have a good time.
我很开心 爸爸
I am, Dad.
你是不是不舒服呀?
Do you feel bad?
我只是有点累了
I'm just a little bit tired.
那你为什么不去睡觉呢?
Then why don't you go to sleep?
我不能去睡觉呢
I can't.
还有很多事等着我做呢
I got too much to do.
你喜欢这间酒店么?
Do you like this hotel?
喜欢
I do.
我很喜欢这儿
I love it.
难道你不喜欢么?
Don't you?
我想我喜欢呢
I guess so.
太好了
Good.
我也希望你能喜欢这儿
I want you to like it here.
我希望咱们能永远住在这儿呢
I wish we could stay here forever...
永远
...and ever...
...and ever.
爸爸?    怎么了?
Dad?     What?
你绝不会伤害妈妈或者我吧 是么?
You would never hurt Mommy or me, would you?
你是什么意思?
What do you mean?
是你妈妈跟你说的么?
Did your mother ever say that to you?
说我会伤害你?
That I would hurt you?
不是呢 爸爸
No, Dad.
你确定
You sure?
是的 爸爸
Yes, Dad.
我爱你 丹尼
I love you, Danny.
我爱你超过
I love you more than anything else...
这世上的一切
...in the whole world...
我绝不会做出任何伤害你的事
...and I would never do anything to hurt you...
绝不
...never.
你知道的 对吧?
You know that, don't you?
知道呢 爸爸
Yes, Dad.
很好
Good.
妈妈 你在里面么?
Mom, are you in there?
怎么回事?
What happened?
亲爱的
Honey...
怎么了?
...what's wrong?
我做了个噩梦
I had the most...
从来没做过这么可怕的梦
...terrible nightmare I ever had.
真的超可怕的
It was the most horrible dream.
真的
Really.
我梦到我
I dreamed that l...
我杀掉了你和丹尼
...that I killed you and Danny.
不过 我不只是杀掉了你
But I didn't just kill you.
我还把你切成了一小块一小块的
I cut you up into little pieces.
天哪
My God.
我肯定是快疯了
I must be losing my mind.
一切都会好的
Everything's going to be all right.
来吧 我们别坐在地板上了
Come on. Let's get up off the floor.
来吧 坐起来
There. Now sit up.
好了
It's okay.
丹尼
Danny!
没事啦
Everything's okay!
去你房间里玩吧
Just go play in your room for a while.
你爸爸只是头疼而已
Your dad's just got a headache.
丹尼 照我说的做 到你自己房里去玩
Danny, mind what I say. Go play in your room.
亲爱的 我先去把他带出去
Honey, let me just go get him out of here.
马上就回来
I'll be right back.
你为什么不听话呢?
Why don't you mind me?
噢 天哪
Oh, my God.
丹尼 你的脖子是怎么回事?
Danny, what happened to your neck?
是你干的
You did this to him...
是不是?!
...didn't you?!
你这个混蛋
You son of a bitch!
是你干的
You did this to him!
是不是?!
Didn't you?!
你怎么下得了手?!
How could you?!
上帝呀 我为了喝一杯什么都做得出来
God! I'd give anything for a drink.
我愿意就为了杯啤酒
I'd give my goddamn soul...
而他妈的出卖自己的灵魂
...for just a glass of beer.
嗨 劳埃德
Hi, Lloyd.
今晚有点慢 不是么?
A little slow tonight, isn't it?
是的 托兰斯先生
Yes it is, Mr. Torrance.
要喝点什么呢呢?
What will it be?
你问我这个真是让我太高兴了 劳埃德
I'm awfully glad you asked me that, Lloyd...
因为我钱包里
...because I just happen to have two twenties...
正好有两张二十的 两张十块的
...and two tens right here in my wallet.
我还怕要明年四月才花得出去了呢
I was afraid they were going to be there until next April.
那么 这样吧
So here's what:
你给我一杯烈性威士忌
You slip me a bottle of bourbon...
就一小杯 要加冰的
...a little glass and some ice.
你能给我一杯的 对吧 劳埃德?
You can do that, can't you, Lloyd?
你还不算太忙 对吧?
You're not too busy, are you?
不忙 先生 一点也不忙
No, sir. I'm not busy at all.
真是个好人
Good man.
你把酒一瓶瓶摆上去
You set them up...
我就把它们一瓶瓶的都喝光
...and I'll knock them back, one by one.
白人教父 劳埃德 我的朋友
White man's burden, Lloyd, my man.
白人教父
White man's burden.
你看 劳埃德
Say, Lloyd...
我最近好象有点晕
...it seems I'm temporarily light.
不管怎样 这地方能用信用卡么?
How's my credit in this joint, anyway?
当然可以 托兰斯先生
Your credit's fine, Mr. Torrance.
真是太棒了
That's swell.
我喜欢你 劳埃德
I like you, Lloyd.
我一直很喜欢你
I always liked you.
你一直都是最好的
You were always the best of them.
真他妈是个最棒的男招待
Best goddamned bartender...
从廷巴克图到缅因州的波特兰都是最棒的
...from Timbuktu to Portland, Maine.
还是俄勒冈州的波特兰 反正都一样
Or Portland, Oregon, for that matter.
谢谢您的夸奖
Thank you for saying so.
我根本没动过他一个手指头 该死的
I never laid a hand on him, goddamn it.
我没有呀
I didn't.
我连他头上的一根头发都不会碰的 该死的
I wouldn't touch one hair on his goddamn little head.
我爱那个小混蛋
I love the little son of a bitch.
我愿意为他付出一切
I'd do anything for him.
他妈的为他付出一切
Any fucking thing for him.
可是那婊子
But that bitch!
只要我还活着
As long as I live...
她就永远不会让我忘记发生过的一切
...she'll never let me forget what happened.
我确实伤害过他一次 好吧?
I did hurt him once, okay?
但那是个意外
It was an accident.
绝对不是有意的
Completely unintentional.
任何人都可能发生的
It could have happened to anybody.
那他妈都是三年前的事了
And it was three goddamn years ago!
那小杂种把我的稿纸扔到地上到处都是
The little fucker had thrown all my papers all over the floor.
我只是想阻止他
All I tried to do was pull him up.
一下子就失手了
A momentary loss of muscular coordination.
我是说
I mean...
每秒多使了几尺磅的力气
...a few extra foot-pounds of energy...
每秒 每秒
...per second, per second.
谢天谢地 你在这儿呀
Thank God you're here.
酒店里除了我们还有别人
There's someone else in the hotel with us.
其中一间房里有个疯女人
There's a crazy woman in one of the rooms.
她想扼死丹尼
She tried to strangle Danny.
你他妈是疯了吧?
Are you out of your fucking mind?
是真的 真的
It's the truth! Really.
我发誓 丹尼告诉我的
I swear it. Danny told me.
他去了间客房
He went up into one of the bedrooms.
门是开着的 他看到那疯女人躺在浴缸里
The door was open, and he saw this crazy woman in the bathtub.
她想扼死他
She tried to strangle him!
哪间房?
Which room was it?
迈阿密十频道
From Channel 10 in Miami...
悠视网络电视获奖新闻报导组
...this is Newswatch with Glen Rinker...
格伦.瑞科尔及安.比斯霍普为您报导
Ann Bishop, and the award-winning Newswatch team.
晚上好 我是悠视网络电视的格伦.瑞科
Good evening. I'm Glen Rinker, Newswatch Ten.
迈阿密受到冬季高原气候影响持续降温
As Miami continues to swelter in a record winter heat wave...
温度已降到九十华氏度
...bringing temperatures to the 90s...
中部地区及山区都被掩埋于雪地之中
...Central and Mountain states are buried in snow.
在科罗拉多州 今晚几小时内降雪量已达到十英尺
In Colorado, 10 inches of snow fell in just a few hours tonight.
已经几乎不可能进入落基山脉
Travel in the Rockies is almost impossible.
机场已关闭 成千上万名乘客被滞留于机场
Airports are shut down, stranding thousands of passengers.
高速公路已为雪堆所堵塞
Highways are blocked by snowdrifts.
铁轨已经结冰
Railroad tracks are frozen.
科罗拉多州官方向悠视网络电视透露
Officials in Colorado tell Newswatch...
至少有三人已由于暴露于暴风雪中致死
at least 3 have been killed by exposure to freezing winds.
科罗拉多州长可能
The governor of Colorado is expected...
会发出天气预警
...to declare a weather emergency.
后备役军人
The National Guard might be called out...
也将上街道清理路面积雪
...to clear streets and roads.
气象站预报今晚到明天
Weather forecasters predict more snow...
降雪量及风力将会进一步加大
...and heavy winds tonight and tomorrow...
气温将降到零度以下
... with temperatures dropping well below zero.
回到佛罗里达 这里的问题恰好相反
Back here in Florida, we've got the opposite problem.
温度及湿度都将继续上升
The heat and humidity are supposed to climb.
当地的海滩肯定会人满为患
Local beaches should be jammed.
气象专家 沃尔特.克龙
Our weather expert, Walter Cronice...
等会将会在悠视为大家预测本地天气
will have the local forecast later on Newswatch.
很抱歉 您拨的电话无法接通
We 're sorry. Your call cannot be completed as dialed.
如果需要帮助 请致电接线员
If you need assistance, please call the operator.
是的 是我
Yes, it's me.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
有什么发现么?
Did you find anything?
不 什么都没有
No. Nothing at all.
我他妈鬼影子都没见到一个
I didn't see one goddamn thing.
你去了丹尼说的那个房间? 二三七号?
You went into the room Danny said? To 237?
是的 去过了
Yes, I did.
你什么都没见到?
And you didn't see anything at all?
绝对什么都没有
Absolutely nothing.
他怎么样了?
How is he?
还在睡觉
He's still asleep.
很好
Good.
等他早上睡醒了就会恢复正常的
I'm sure he'll be himself again in the morning.
你确定你去对了房间?
Are you sure it was the right room?
我是说 或许是丹尼搞错了
I mean, maybe Danny made a mistake.
他肯定进了那个房间
He must have gone in that room.
门是开着的 灯也亮着
The door was open, the lights were on.
那我就不明白了
I just don't understand it.
那他身上那些瘀伤是怎么回事呢?
What about those bruises on his neck?
肯定有人伤害了他的
Somebody did that to him.
我想
I think...
是他自己干的
...he did it to himself.
不
No.
不可能
That's not possible.
如果他说的话不是真的
Once you rule out his version of what happened...
那就没别的解释了
...there is no other explanation.
是么?
Is there?
不管是怎么回事
Whatever the explanation is...
我想 我们
...l think we...
都得带丹尼离开这儿
...have to get Danny out of here.
带他离开这儿?
Get him out of here?
你是说
You mean...
离开酒店?
...just leave the hotel?
你们俩真是
It is so...
会在我终于有机会做成点事的时候
...typical of you to create a problem like this...
搞出麻烦来
...when I finally have a chance to accomplish something!
我现在正真正在干事业
When I'm really into my work!
如果我想现在就回去的话 就回得去么?
I could really write my own ticket if I went back now, couldn't l?
开着铲雪当洗车
Shoveling out driveways, work in a car wash.
你觉得怎么样呀?
Any of that appeal to you?
我一直让你把我的生活搞得一团糟
I have let you fuck up my life so far...
不过 这次我不会让你毁了我的
...but I am not going to let you fuck this up.
晚上好 林务局
Good evening. Forest Service.
我叫狄克.哈罗朗
My name is Dick Hallorann.
我是远望酒店的厨师长
I'm the head chef at the Overlook Hotel.
晚上好 有什么能帮到你的么?
Good evening. What can I do for you?
我想打个紧急电话到酒店上去
I've been trying to make an urgent phone call up there...
不过接线员说电话线装已经吹倒了
but the operator said that the phone lines are down.
那附近很多电话线桩都由于暴风雪倒塌了
A lot of lines around here are down due to the storm.
我不想给您造成任何麻烦的
I hate to put you through any trouble...
不过有家人还待在酒店里 而且还有个小孩子
...but there's a family up there all by themselves with a young kid.
就现在这种暴风雪袭击的情况下
And with this storm and everything...
如果你们能用无线电跟他们联系下 我将非常感谢
I'd appreciate it if you'd give them a call on your radio...
就看看他们是不是还好
...just to see if everything's okay.
我很高兴为您致电他们
I'll be glad to do that.
您二十分钟之后再打来好么?
Why don't you call me back in about 20 minutes?
非常感谢 我会的
Thank you very much. I'll do that.
好的 先生
All right, sir.
晚上好 托兰斯先生
Good evening, Mr. Torrance.
晚上好
Good evening.
嗨 劳埃德
Hi, Lloyd.
我刚才走开了 不过现在又回来了
Been away, but now I'm back.
晚上好 托兰斯先生
Good evening, Mr. Torrance.
很高兴见到您
It's good to see you.
回来感觉真好 劳埃德
It's good to be back, Lloyd.
想喝点什么酒 先生?
What'll it be, sir?
给杯能让我一醉方休的
Hair of the dog that bit me.
那就来杯波本威士忌加冰块
Bourbon on the rocks.
就是它了
That'll do her.
免费享用 托兰斯先生
No charge to you, Mr. Torrance.
免费享用?
No charge?
你的钱在这儿派不上用处了
Your money's no good here.
有人帮您付过了
Orders from the house.
有人付过了
喝吧 托兰斯先生
Drink up, Mr. Torrance.
我想知道是谁帮我付的帐 劳埃德
I'm the kind of man likes to know who's buying their drinks, Lloyd.
你就不用管这个了 托兰斯先生
It's not a matter that concerns you, Mr. Torrance.
至少 现在不必要知道
At least, not at this point.
你说了算 劳埃德
Anything you say, Lloyd.
你说了算
Anything you say.
噢 天哪 抱歉 先生
Oh, dear! I'm so sorry, sir.
噢 天哪 天哪
Oh, dear. Oh, dear.
看我把你的夹克搞得一团糟 先生
I've made an awful mess of your jacket, sir.
没关系的 我有很多夹克
That's all right. I've got plenty of jackets.
这是荷兰蛋酒 恐怕会留下印迹了
I'm afraid it's advocaat, sir. It tends to stain.
荷兰蛋酒 是么?
Advocaat, is it?
是的 先生 我想最好是
Yes, sir. I think the best thing...
我陪您到男洗手间去
...is to come along to the gentlemen's room...
弄点水洗干净吧 先生
...and we'll get some water to it, sir.
好象你自己身上也弄到了
Looks like you might have got a spot of it on yourself...
侍应老伙计
...Jeevesy old boy.
没关系 先生 您最要紧
That doesn't matter, sir. You're the important one.
你真是个大好人
Awfully nice of you to say.
其实 今晚来参加宴会之前
Of course, I intended to change my jacket this evening...
我就想换到这身衣服的
...before the fish and goose soiree.
非常明智 先生 非常明智
Very wise, sir. Very wise.
好了 我来帮你
Here. I'll just...
把门打开 侍应
...hold this for you there, Jeevesy.
谢谢您 先生 谢谢您
Thank you, sir. Thank you.
看看弄点水是不是能洗得掉
Let's see if we can improve this with a little water, sir.
好吧 我把
All right. I'll just...
波本威士忌和蛋酒都放在这儿
...set my bourbon and advocaat down right there.
一会就好了
Won't keep you a moment.
好的
Fine.
他们都怎么叫你的 侍应
What do they call you, Jeevesy?
格兰蒂 先生 戴伯特.格兰蒂
Grady, sir. Delbert Grady.
格兰蒂?
Grady?
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
戴伯特.格兰蒂
Delbert Grady.
是的 先生
That's right, sir.
格兰蒂先生
Mr. Grady...
我以前在哪儿见过你么?
...haven't I seen you somewhere before?
怎么呢 不 先生 我觉得没见过
Why, no, sir. I don't believe so.
快弄掉了呢 先生
It's coming off now, sir.
格兰蒂先生
Mr. Grady...
你以前是不是做过这儿的看守?
...weren't you once the caretaker here?
怎么 没有呢 先生 没有
Why, no, sir. I don't believe so.
你结婚了 对么 格兰蒂先生
You a married man, are you, Mr. Grady?
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
我有老婆 还有两个女儿
I have a wife and two daughters, sir.
那么
And...
他们现在在哪儿
...where are they now?
就在这附近吧 我现在也不太清楚
They're somewhere around. I'm not quite sure at the moment.
你就说在这儿做过看守
You were the caretaker here.
我认得出你来
I recognize you.
我在报纸上见过你的照片
I saw your picture in the newspapers.
你
You...
把你妻子和女儿都剁成了一块块的
...chopped your wife and daughter up into little bits.
而且
And...
之后你还打爆了自己的脑袋
...then you blew your brains out.
真奇怪 先生
That's strange, sir.
我完全想不起来有这种事
I don't have any recollection of that at all.
格兰蒂先生
Mr. Grady...
你以前确实是这儿的看守
...you were the caretaker here.
很抱歉 不能附和您 先生
I'm sorry to differ with you, sir.
不过 您
But you...
才是看守呀
...are the caretaker.
您一直都是看守
You've always been the caretaker.
我早该知道的 先生
I should know, sir.
我一直都在这儿
I've always been here.
你知道么 托兰斯先生
Did you know, Mr. Torrance...
您的儿子
...that your son...
正准备跟外面的人取得联络
...is attempting to bring an outside party...
对付现在的状况
...into this situation?
你知道么?
Did you know that?
是真的 托兰斯先生
He is, Mr. Torrance.
跟谁?
Who?
跟个黑人
A nigger.
黑人?
A nigger?
黑人
A nigger...
厨子
...cook.
怎样?
How?
你儿子
Your son...
有特殊的天赋
...has a very great talent.
相信你并没有意识到那有多厉害
I don't think you are aware how great it is.
不过他正准备运用这一天赋
But he is attempting to use that very talent...
来对抗你的意志
...against your will.
那么
Well...
他是个非常任性的孩子
...he is a very willful boy.
他确实是 托兰斯先生
Indeed he is, Mr. Torrance.
非常任性的孩子
A very willful boy.
真是个一个非常
A rather...
淘气的孩子
...naughty boy...
要是我有那么大胆子就好了 先生
...if I may be so bold, sir.
都是他妈妈惯的
It's his mother.
她
She...
老是碍手碍脚
...interferes.
或许他们需要
Perhaps they need a good...
被好好教育教育了
...talking-to.
如果
If...
您不介意我这么说的话
...you don't mind my saying so.
或许
Perhaps...
应该再严厉些
...a bit more.
我的女儿们 先生
My girls, sir...
她们最开始也不在乎远望酒店
...they didn't care for the Overlook at first.
其中一个还偷了一盒火柴
One of them actually stole a pack of matches...
想把这儿给烧掉
...and tried to burn it down.
但是我
But l...
及时纠正了她们的错误 先生
...corrected them, sir.
而且 在我妻子试图阻止我履行职责的时候
And when my wife tried to prevent me from doing my duty...
我
...l...
也及时纠正了她
...corrected her.
KDK 1呼叫KDK 12
KDK 1 calling KDK 12.
有收到么?
Are you receiving me?
KDK 1呼叫KDK 12
This is KDK 1 calling KDK 12.
KDK 1 calling KDK 12.
请问收到了么?
Do you read me?
KDK 1呼叫KDK 12
This is KDK 1 calling KDK 12.
KDK 1 calling KDK 12.
收到么?
Are you receiving me?
您现在收听的是六十三频道，哈尔和查理在丹佛为您播音
You're with Hal and Charlie on Radio 63, KHOW, Denver.
今天天气非常恶劣
And we have a bad day out there.
整个丹佛山区都受到暴风雪的肆虐
Heavy snow throughout the Denver metro area.
许多通往
Many mountain passes...
狼溪和红山的路都已关闭
... Wolf Creek and Red Mountain passes are closed...
艾森豪威尔隧道
...and the chain law is in effect at the Eisenhower Tunnel.
我们从新闻局获知
We hear from the news department...
只有几班飞机能在斯塔普斯勒顿机场降落
...only a few flights are landing at Stapleton Airport...
在如此暴风雪的肆虐下
...and with storms like this...
我想在几个小时后整个机场都会关闭
...l guess the entire airport will be closed within the hour.
今天暴风雪还将持续 而且气象局
The storm will continue through the day and the Weather Service...
向畜牧业者及旅行者发出公告
...has declared a stockman's and traveler's advisory...
建议他们远离整个丹佛山区
...for all areas outlying the Denver metro region.
你觉得怎么样?
How do you like it?
你在这下面干吗?
What are you doing down here?
我只是
I just...
想
...wanted...
跟你谈谈
...to talk to you.
好吧
Okay.
谈吧
Let's talk.
你想谈什么?
What do you want to talk about?
我真的记不起来了
I can't really remember.
你记不起来了
You can't remember.
不
No...
记不起来了
...l can't.
或许是想跟我谈谈丹尼?
Maybe it was about Danny?
或许是想跟我谈谈丹尼
Maybe it was about him.
我想我们应该谈谈丹尼
I think we should discuss Danny.
我想
I think...
我们应该讨论下要怎么处理他
... we should discuss what should be done with him.
应该怎么处理他呢?
What should be done with him?
我不知道
I don't know.
我觉得你没说实话
I don't think that's true.
我觉得你很清楚
I think you have some very definite ideas...
要拿丹尼怎么办
...about what should be done with Danny.
我想知道你是怎么想的
And I'd like to know what they are.
那么 我
Well, l...
我想他应该去看医生
...l think maybe he should be taken to a doctor.
你觉得或许他该去看医生
You think "maybe" he should be taken to a doctor?
你觉得或许他该什么时候去看医生呢?
When do you think "maybe" he should be taken to a doctor?
尽快吧?
As soon as possible?
"As soon as possible?"
求你了
Please.
你觉得他现在身体状况很不好
You believe his health might be at stake.
是的
Yes.
而且你很关心他
And you are concerned about him.
那你关心我么?
And are you concerned about me?
我当然关心你
Of course I am.
你当然关心我
Of course you are!
那你有没有考虑过我的职责?
Have you ever thought about my responsibilities?
你在说什么呀?
What are you talking about?
你有没有任何时候
Have you ever had a single moment's...
考虑过我的职责?
...thought about my responsibilities?
你有没有任何时候考虑过
Have you ever thought for a single moment...
我对我老板应当承担的职责?
...about my responsibilities to my employers?!
你到底有没有想过
Has is ever occurred to you...
我承诺要在五月一日之前都看守这间酒店?
...that I have agreed to look after the hotel until May 1st?
你到底在不在乎
Does it matter to you at all...
老板对我寄予了所有的信任
...that the owners have placed their complete confidence in me...
你到底在不在乎我是签了合同的
...and that I have signed a letter of agreement...
是接受了我所需要承担的职责的?
...in which I've accepted that responsibility?
你有没有稍微考虑过
Do you have the slightest idea...
道德和伦理界限? 有没有?!
...what a moral and ethical principal is? Do you?!
你有没有考虑过一下 如果我不履行职责
Has it ever occurred to you what would happen to my future...
会对我的将来造成什么样的影响?
...if I fail to live up to my responsibilities?
你到底有没有想过? 有没有?!
Has it ever occurred to you? Has it?!
离我远点
Stay away from me!
为什么?
Why?
我只是想回自己房间去了
I just want to go back to my room.
为什么?
Why?
那么
Well...
我很困惑
...I'm very confused.
我只是想有个机会把所有事都想清楚
And I just need a chance to think things over.
你他妈这一辈子都在考虑考虑
You've had your whole fucking life to think things over!
现在花多几分钟去考虑又会怎样?
What good's a few minutes more going to do you now?
离我远点
Stay away from me!
求你了
Please!
别伤害我
Don't hurt me.
我不会伤害你的
I'm not going to hurt you.
离我远点
Stay away from me!
走开
Stay away!
亲爱的
Darling.
我的生命之光
Light of my life.
我不会伤害你的
I'm not going to hurt you.
你还没让我说完呢
You didn't let me finish my sentence.
我说了 我不会伤害你的
I said, "I'm not going to hurt you."
我就是想打烂你的脑袋
I'm just going to bash your brains in.
就想在这儿把你的脑袋给打烂
I'm going to bash them right the fuck in.
走开
Stay away from me!
我不会伤害你的
I'm not going to hurt you.
离我远点
Stay away from me!
走开
Stay away!
求你了
Please!
别对着我挥球棒
Stop swinging the bat.
走开
Stay away from me.
把那球棒放下 温蒂
Put that bat down, Wendy.
Stop it!
住手
Give me the bat.
求你了
Please!
走开    把球棒给我
Stay away!     Give me the bat.
住手
Stop it!
把棒子给我
Give me the bat.
走开点     别再挥球棒了
Stay away from me.     Stop swinging the bat.
快住手
Please stop!
把球棒给我
Give me the bat.
走开呀
Stay away from me.
住手     快给我
Stop it!     Give me the bat.
该死的
Goddamn--!
你在干吗?
What are you doing?
等等
Wait a minute.
你在干吗?
What are you doing?
等等呀
Wait a minute!
你在干吗?
What are you doing?
开门
Open the door!
他妈的
Goddamn it!
让我出去 你他妈把门给我打开
Let me out of here! Open the goddamn door!
温蒂 听着
Wendy, listen.
让我出去 我不会跟你计较的
Let me out and I'll forget the whole goddamn thing.
就当什么都没发生过
It'll be just like nothing ever happened.
温蒂 宝贝
Wendy. Baby.
你真的把我脑袋打伤了
I think you hurt my head real bad.
我头很晕
I'm dizzy.
需要看医生
I need a doctor.
亲爱的
Honey.
别把我丢在这儿
Don't leave me in here.
我现在要走了
I'm going to go now.
我准备今天开雪地车
I'm going to try...
把丹尼
...to get Danny down the Sidewinder...
带下赛得万能达去
...in the Snowcat today.
我要带他去看医生
I'll bring back a doctor.
现在就走
I'm going to go now.
给你个惊喜吧
You've got a big surprise coming to you.
你哪儿都去不了
You're not going anywhere.
去检查下雪地车和无线电  你就知道我说的是什么惊喜了
Go check out the Snowcat and the radio and you'll see what I mean.
去看看吧
Go check it out.
Go check it out!
去看看吧
Go check it out.
我是格兰蒂 托兰斯先生
It's Grady, Mr. Torrance.
戴伯特.格兰蒂
Delbert Grady.
格兰蒂?
Grady?
哈罗 格兰蒂
Hello, Grady.
托兰斯先生
Mr. Torrance...
我看你很难处理得了
...l see you can hardly have taken care of the...
我们所谈过的问题呀
...business we discussed.
没必要一直戳我的痛处吧 格兰蒂先生
No need to rub it in, Mr. Grady.
只要我一出去 就能搞得定
I'll deal with that situation as soon as I get out of here.
真的能么 托兰斯先生?
Will you indeed, Mr. Torrance?
我很怀疑
I wonder.
我真的很怀疑
I have my doubts.
我 还有其他人开始觉得
I, and others, have come to believe...
你的心根本就不属于这儿
...that your heart is not in this.
你对这儿根本就没兴趣
That you haven't the belly for it.
再给我次机会证明自己吧 格兰蒂先生
Just give me one more chance to prove it, Mr. Grady.
我就这么点要求
That's all I ask.
你妻子看来比我们想象的要坚强得多 托兰斯先生
Your wife appears to be stronger than we imagined, Mr. Torrance.
而且比想象的更
Somewhat more...
足智多谋
...resourceful.
她好象比你要强得多
She seems to have got the better of you.
暂时的 格兰蒂先生
For the moment, Mr. Grady.
只是暂时的
Only for the moment.
恐怕你不得不拿出最强硬的手段
I fear you will have to deal with this matter...
来处理现在这种状况了 托兰斯先生
...in the harshest possible way, Mr. Torrance.
恐怕
I fear...
这也是你唯一能做的了
...that is the only thing to do.
我可没期望过
There's nothing I look forward to...
心平气和的解决这个问题 格兰蒂先生
...with greater pleasure, Mr. Grady.
你确定 是么 托兰斯先生?
You give your word on that, do you, Mr. Torrance?
我保证
I give you my word.
Redrum
丹尼 停下来
Danny, stop it!
温蒂 我回来了
Wendy. I'm home.
出来 管你在哪儿 快出来
Come out, come out, wherever you are.
我出不来
I can't get out.
快跑
Run!
快跑呀 藏起来
Run and hide!
快跑
Run!
快
Quick!
小猪猪 小猪猪 快让我进来 (儿歌)
Little pigs, little pigs, let me come in.
不行 绝对不会开门的
Not by the hair on your chinny-chin-chin?
那我就呼呼呼呼
Then I'll huff...
吹呀吹
...and I'll puff...
突然进到你的房子里来
...and I'll blow your house in!
求你了
Please!
别
Don't!
住手
Stop it!
小家伙在这里呀
Here's Johnny!
哈罗?
Hello?
有人在么?
Anybody here?
哈罗?
Hello?
有人在么?
Anybody here?
丹尼小子
Danny-boy!
我来了
I'm coming!
我来了 丹尼
I'm coming, Dan!
开派对 是吧?
Great party, isn't it?
我来了
I'm coming!!
你跑不掉了
You can't get away!
我就在你背后
I'm right behind you!
妈妈     丹尼 过来
Mommy!     Danny, come here!
妈妈
Mommy.
在哪儿?
Where...?